const questionset1 = [{
    question: "Which of the following data type is supported by c++ but not in c?",
    options: ["Int","Bool","Double","Float"],
    answer: "Bool"
},
{
    question: "Identify the correct syntax for declaring arrays in c++",
    options: ["Array arr[10]", "Array{10}", "Int arr[10]", "Int arr"],
    answer: "Int arr[10]"
},
{
    question: "Which of the following is address of operator",
    options: ["*", "&", "||", "&&"],
    answer: "&"
},
{
    question: "Identify the correct example for a pre increment operator",
    options: ["++N", "N++", "--n", "N--"],
    answer: "++N"
},
{
    question: "Identify the scope of resolution operator",
    options: [":", "::", "?", "None"],
    answer: "::"
},


]


const questionset2 = [
    {
        question: "Choose the correct default return value of function",
        options: ["Int", "Void", "Char", "Float"],
        answer: "Int"
    },
    {
        question: "When can an inline function be expanded",
        options: ["Runtime", "Compile time", "Never gets expanded", "All the above"],
        answer: "Compile time"
    },
    {
        question: "Identify the correct function from which the execution of C++ program starts",
        options: ["New()", "Start()", "Pow()", "Main()"],
        answer: "Main()"
    },
    {
        question: "The constant in C++ are also known as",
        options: ["Preprocessor", "Literals", "Const", "None"],
        answer: "Literals"
    }
]


const questionset1written = [
    {
        question: "What is the number of parameters that a default constructor requires?"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the Hello"
    }
]

const questionset2written = [
    {
        question: "What is the number of parameters that a default constructor requires?"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the Hello"
    }
]

export {questionset1, questionset2, questionset1written, questionset2written}
